[{question: 'When a user views a page containing a JavaScript program, which machine actually executes the script?',A: 'The User’s machine running a Web browser',B: 'The Web server',C: 'A central machine deep within Netscape’s corporate offices',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: '______ JavaScript is also called client-side JavaScript.',A: 'Microsoft',B: 'Navigator',C: 'LiveWire',D: 'Native',Ans: 'B'}, {question: '__________ JavaScript is also called server-side JavaScript.',A: 'Microsoft',B: 'Navigator',C: 'LiveWire',D: 'Native',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'What are variables used for in JavaScript Programs?',A: 'Storing numbers, dates, or other values',B: 'Varying randomly',C: 'Causing high-school algebra flashbacks',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: '_____ JavaScript statements embedded in an HTML page can respond to user events such as mouse-clicks, form input, and page navigation.',A: 'Client-side',B: 'Server-side',C: 'Local',D: 'Native',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'What should appear at the very end of your JavaScript?',The &lt;script LANGUAGE=”JavaScript”&gt;tag',A: 'The &lt;/script&gt;',B: 'The &lt;script&gt;',C: 'The END statement',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Which of the following can’t be done with client-side JavaScript?',A: 'Validating a form',B: 'Sending a form’s contents by email',C: 'Storing the form’s contents to a database file on the server',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'Which of the following are capabilities of functions in JavaScript?',A: 'Return a value',B: 'Accept parameters and Return a value',C: 'Accept parameters',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'Which of the following is not a valid JavaScript variable name?',A: '2names',B: '_first_and_last_names',C: 'FirstAndLast',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: '______ tag is an extension to HTML that can enclose any number of JavaScript statements.',A: '&lt;SCRIPT&gt;',B: '&lt;BODY&gt;',C: '&lt;HEAD&gt;',D: '&lt;TITLE&gt;',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'How does JavaScript store dates in a date object?',A: 'The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970',B: 'The number of days since January 1st, 1900',C: 'The number of seconds since Netscape’s public stock offering.',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Which of the following attribute can hold the JavaScript version?',A: 'LANGUAGE',B: 'SCRIPT',C: 'VERSION',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'What is the correct JavaScript syntax to write “Hello World”?',A: 'System.out.println(“Hello World”)',B: 'println (“Hello World”)',C: 'document.write(“Hello World”)',D: 'response.write(“Hello World”)',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'Which of the following way can be used to indicate the LANGUAGE attribute?',A: '&lt;LANGUAGE=”JavaScriptVersion”&gt;',B: '&lt;SCRIPT LANGUAGE=”JavaScriptVersion”&gt;',C: '&lt;SCRIPT LANGUAGE=”JavaScriptVersion”&gt; JavaScript statements…&lt;/SCRIPT&gt;',D: '&lt;SCRIPT LANGUAGE=”JavaScriptVersion”!&gt; JavaScript statements…&lt;/SCRIPT&gt;',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?',A: '&lt;js&gt;',B: '&lt;scripting&gt;',C: '&lt;script&gt;',D: '&lt;javascript&gt;',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called ” abc.js”?',A: '&lt;script href=” abc.js”&gt;',B: '&lt;script name=” abc.js”&gt;',C: '&lt;script src=” abc.js”&gt;',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'Which types of image maps can be used with JavaScript?',A: 'Server-side image maps',B: 'Client-side image maps',C: 'Server-side image maps and Client-side image maps',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'B'}, {question: 'Which of the following navigator object properties is the same in both Netscape and IE?',A: 'navigator.appCodeName',B: 'navigator.appName',C: 'navigator.appVersion',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Which is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?',A: 'var txt = new Array(1:”tim”,2:”kim”,3:”jim”)',B: 'var txt = new Array:1=(“tim”)2=(“kim”)3=(“jim”)',C: 'var txt = new Array(“tim”,”kim”,”jim”)',D: 'var txt = new Array=”tim”,”kim”,”jim”',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'What does the &lt;noscript&gt; tag do?',A: 'Enclose text to be displayed by non-JavaScript browsers.',B: 'Prevents scripts on the page from executing.',C: 'Describes certain low-budget movies.',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'If para1 is the DOM object for a paragraph, what is the correct syntax to change the text within the paragraph?',A: '“New Text”?',B: 'para1.value=”New Text”;',C: 'para1.firstChild.nodeValue= “New Text”;',D: 'para1.nodeValue=”New Text”;',Ans: 'B'}, {question: 'JavaScript entities start with _______ and end with _________.',A: 'Semicolon, colon',B: 'Semicolon, Ampersand',C: 'Ampersand, colon',D: 'Ampersand, semicolon',Ans: 'D'}, {question: 'Which of the following best describes JavaScript?',A: 'a low-level programming language.',B: 'a scripting language precompiled in the browser.',C: 'a compiled scripting language.',D: 'an object-oriented scripting language.',Ans: 'D'}, {question: 'Choose the server-side JavaScript object?',A: 'FileUpLoad',B: 'Function',C: 'File',D: 'Date',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'Choose the client-side JavaScript object?',A: 'Database',B: 'Cursor',C: 'Client',D: 'FileUpLoad',Ans: 'D'}, {question: 'Which of the following is not considered a JavaScript operator?',A: 'new',B: 'this',C: 'delete',D: 'typeof',Ans: 'B'}, {question: '______method evaluates a string of JavaScript code in the context of the specified object.',A: 'Eval',B: 'ParseInt',C: 'ParseFloat',D: 'Efloat',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Which of the following event fires when the form element loses the focus: '&lt;button&gt;, &lt;input&gt;, &lt;label&gt;, &lt;select&gt;, &lt;textarea&gt;?',A: 'onfocus',B: 'onblur',C: 'onclick',D: 'ondblclick',Ans: 'B'}, {question: 'The syntax of Eval is ________________',A: '[objectName.]eval(numeriC:',B: '[objectName.]eval(string)',C: '[EvalName.]eval(string)',D: '[EvalName.]eval(numeriC:',Ans: 'B'}, {question: 'JavaScript is interpreted by _________',A: 'Client',B: 'Server',C: 'Object',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Using _______ statement is how you test for a specific condition.',A: 'Select',B: 'If',C: 'Switch',D: 'For',Ans: 'B'}, {question: 'Which of the following is the structure of an if statement?',A: 'if (conditional expression is true) thenexecute this codeend if',B: 'if (conditional expression is true)execute this codeend if',C: 'if (conditional expression is true) {question: 'then execute this code&gt;-&gt;'}, ',D: 'if (conditional expression is true) then {question: 'execute this code'}, ',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'How to create a Date object in JavaScript?',A: 'dateObjectName = new Date([parameters])',B: 'dateObjectName.new Date([parameters])',C: 'dateObjectName := new Date([parameters])',D: 'dateObjectName Date([parameters])',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'The _______ method of an Array object adds and/or removes elements from an array.',A: 'Reverse',B: 'Shift',C: 'Slice',D: 'Splice',Ans: 'D'}, {question: 'To set up the window to capture all Click events, we use which of the following statement?',A: 'window.captureEvents(Event.CLICK);',B: 'window.handleEvents (Event.CLICK);',C: 'window.routeEvents(Event.CLICK );',D: 'window.raiseEvents(Event.CLICK );',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Which tag(s) can handle mouse events in Netscape?',A: '&lt;IMG&gt;',B: '&lt;A&gt;',C: '&lt;BR&gt;',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'B'}, {question: '____________ is the tainted property of a window object.',A: 'Pathname',B: 'Protocol',C: 'Defaultstatus',D: 'Host',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'To enable data tainting, the end user sets the _________ environment variable.',A: 'ENABLE_TAINT',B: 'MS_ENABLE_TAINT',C: 'NS_ENABLE_TAINT',D: 'ENABLE_TAINT_NS',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'In JavaScript, _________ is an object of the target language data type that encloses an object of the source language.',A: 'a wrapper',B: 'a link',C: 'a cursor',D: 'a form',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'When a JavaScript object is sent to Java, the runtime engine creates a Java wrapper of type ___________',A: 'ScriptObject',B: 'JSObject',C: 'JavaObject',D: 'Jobject',Ans: 'B'}, {question: '_______ class provides an interface for invoking JavaScript methods and examining JavaScript properties.',A: 'ScriptObject',B: 'JSObject',C: 'JavaObject',D: 'Jobject',Ans: 'B'}, {question: '_________ is a wrapped Java array, accessed from within JavaScript code.',A: 'JavaArray',B: 'JavaClass',C: 'JavaObject',D: 'JavaPackage',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'A ________ object is a reference to one of the classes in a Java package, such as netscape.javascript .',A: 'JavaArray',B: 'JavaClass',C: 'JavaObject',D: 'JavaPackage',Ans: 'B'}, {question: 'The JavaScript exception is available to the Java code as an instance of __________',A: 'netscape.javascript.JSObject',B: 'netscape.javascript.JSException',C: 'netscape.plugin.JSException',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'B'}, {question: 'To automatically open the console when a JavaScript error occurs which of the following is added to prefs.js?',A: 'user_pref(” javascript.console.open_on_error”, false);',B: 'user_pref(“javascript.console.open_error “, true);',C: 'user_pref(“javascript.console.open_error “, false);',D: 'user_pref(“javascript.console.open_on_error”, true);',Ans: 'D'}, {question: 'To open a dialog box each time an error occurs, which of the following is added to prefs.js?',A: 'user_pref(“javascript.classic.error_alerts”, true);',B: 'user_pref(“javascript.classic.error_alerts “, false);',C: 'user_pref(“javascript.console.open_on_error “, true);',D: 'user_pref(“javascript.console.open_on_error “, false);',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'The syntax of a blur method in a button object is ______________',A: 'Blur()',B: 'Blur(contrast)',C: 'Blur(value)',D: 'Blur(depth)',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'The syntax of capture events method for document object is ______________',A: 'captureEvents()',B: 'captureEvents(args eventType)',C: 'captureEvents(eventType)',D: 'captureEvents(eventVal)',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'The syntax of close method for document object is ______________',A: 'Close(doC:',B: 'Close(object)',C: 'Close(val)',D: 'Close()',Ans: 'D'}, {question: '&lt;script type=”text/javascript”&gt;',x=4+”4″;',document.write(x);',&lt;/script&gt;'}, {question: '&lt;script&gt;',document.write(navigator.appCodeName);',&lt;/script&gt;',A: 'get code name of the browser of a visitor',B: 'set code name of the browser of a visitor',C: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Scripting language are',A: 'High Level Programming language',B: 'Assembly Level programming language',C: 'Machine level programming language',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'Which best explains getSelection()?',A: 'Returns the VALUE of a selected OPTION.',B: 'Returns document.URL of the window in focus.',C: 'Returns the value of cursor-selected text',D: 'Returns the VALUE of a checked radio input.',Ans: 'C'}, {question: 'Choose the client-side JavaScript object:',A: 'Database',B: 'Cursor',C: 'Client',D: 'FileUpLoad',Ans: 'D'}, {question: 'What is mean by “this” keyword in javascript?',A: 'It refers current object',B: 'It referes previous object',C: 'It is variable which contains value',D: 'None of the above',Ans: 'A'}, {question: 'In JavaScript, Window.prompt() method return true or false value ?',A: 'False',B: 'True',Ans: 'A]